Congratulations on getting through your first batch of lessons.
恭喜你终于学完了第一阶段的课程
Next on your agenda is your first project, trading with momentum,
接下来你将完成第一个实战项目 即基于动量的交易策略
where you'll implement a momentum trading strategy and perform
你将制定一个动量交易策略
a statistical test to conclude if there's alpha in the signal.
并进行统计学检验 判断是否存在 alpha 信号
That sounds like a really interesting project.
听起来是很有趣的项目
Does a bode on the learning we've been doing up until now?
这个项目是以我们到目前为止所学的知识为基础吗？
It does. This project will give you an overview of the Quant workflow.
是的这个项目将使你大致了解量化分析师的工作流程
By preprocessing data with pandas,
你将使用 Pandas 预处理数据
implementing a trading signal,
生成交易信号
and evaluating it's performance.
并评估投资组合的业绩
Sounds like students will get a chance to
听起来学员将有机会
use all the skills they've been building up until now,
运用到目前为止掌握的技能
but in a really industry-relevant way.
并且以与行业相关的项目形式进行实践练习
Completely. We'll use this foundation in later lessons
是的我们将在后面的课程中用到这些基础知识
where you'll learn more advanced techniques to generate trading signals,
之后 你将学习更加高级的技巧来生成交易信号
construct a portfolio, and evaluate its performance.
构建投资组合并评估投资组合的业绩
That's awesome. Projects are a super powerful learning tool,
很棒实战项目是很强大的学习工具
they give you a chance to bring together all the skills and knowledge you've built
使你能够综合运用到目前为止所学的所有技能
up until now and apply them in new and interesting ways.
并以有趣的新方式运用这些技能
Totally. I love doing projects.
没错我喜欢做项目
They certainly can feel a bit challenging,
做项目肯定有挑战性
but even though I don't always see the solution straight away,
虽然有时候不能立即找到解决方案
they help me grow in really meaningful ways.
但是有助于我不断成长
Totally. That's a great point.
是的有道理
Since projects are these big learning opportunities,
因为做项目是很好的学习机会
it's totally normal to find them challenging.
做的过程中感到很棘手完全正常
Luckily, in your Nanodegree Program,
幸运的是 在纳米学位课程中
you get to iterate on your projects just like you do with work in the real world.
你可以不断改进项目 就像在实际工作中一样
That's right. You'll get personalized feedback on each project you do from
是的对于每个项目 你都能获得
our expert project reviewers that will help you see what
专业项目审阅专家的反馈 他们可以告诉你
you've learned already and how you can keep learning and improving your work.
你已经掌握的知识以及如何继续学习和改进项目
If your project doesn't meet the specifications the first
如果第一次甚至多次项目都没有满足规范
time or even a number times beyond that, that's totally normal.
也完全没关系
Yeah. Again, projects themselves are meant to stretch your knowledge and skills,
是的重申下 项目本身旨在巩固你的知识和技能
not just give you a chance to show off what you've already learned.
不仅仅用来展示你所学的知识
It's the same as with the quizzes in the Udacity classroom,
项目与教室里的小测验一样
you get to play around and practice with them,
你可以不断练习
trying them as many times as you want to or need to to keep growing.
或多次尝试改进项目
Everything you do at Udacity is intended to help you learn,
在优达学城 一切都是为了帮助你学习
and you are in the driver's seat.
这场学习之旅由你来驾驭
Good luck with project one, and have fun.
希望你能顺利完成第一个项目 加油